http://www.calstatela-fcu.org/about-us/privacy-statement

SKIP TO CONTENT
We have resumed normal business hours: Mon – Fri 9am – 5pm (closed Sat). Learn More Appointments required for loans or new accounts. Make AppointmentWe will close at 1pm on Thursday, December 24 and be closed on Friday, December 25 for the Christmas holiday.
Search:
Home
>
About Us
>
Privacy Statement
Privacy Statement
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read the Opt Out notice carefully to understand what we do.
California law provides that a consumer has the right to control the sharing of personal and financial information with outside companies the financial institution contracts with to provide financial products and services. To exercise your right, refer to the separate notice, Important Privacy Choices for Consumers.
When you access our webite, information about your computer hardware and software is automatically collected, which can include: browser type, access times and your Internet Protocol (IP) address. We use this information for the operation of our site, to maintain quality of service, and to provide general statistics regarding the use of our site.
Effective March 2015, this statement will no longer be provided annually to members in statements. Changes will be published annually to this website, or copies of the privacy disclosures may be requested by calling 323-505-2600.
Federal Privacy PolicyState Privacy Policy
Apply for a Membership
We welcome CSULA students, staff and faculty as well as residents from the surrounding communities. Find out your eligibility and join us today!
APPLY FOR A LOAN
We have a loan for almost any situation, so feel free to browse our loan products and services or apply now if you're ready!
Online Banking
If you have created new credentials, please login here:
Go
Forgot Password [?]   Online Enrollment [?]ACCESS CREDIT CARD ACCOUNT
Find an ATM
HomeAbout Us
Who Can JoinOur HistoryCredit Union DifferenceCredit Union MovementMission and VisionAnnual MeetingVolunteersMeet the CEOResourcesFAQsPrivacy StatementEn EspañolAccessibilityAccounts
CheckingBusiness CheckingSavings AccountsHoliday SaverCertificatesIRAsCoverdell Education Savings AccountsSavings RatesInsured FundsReorder ChecksLoans
Personal LoansPersonal LoansOverdraft Protection & Line of CreditDebt ConsolidationShare Secured LoansEarly PaydayVehicle LoansAuto LoansRV, Motorcycle, WatercraftMechanical Repair Coverage & GAPVISA Credit CardSkip-A-PaymentCredit Life & Disability InsuranceMake a Payment or TransferReal Estate LoansServices
Find an ATMFree Online Banking & Bill PayerMobile Bankinge-StatementsVISA Debit ATM CardVerified By VISAAutomatic Deposit OptionsWire TransferReorder ChecksInsuranceGroup Legal ServicesTrustage Health InsuranceForms & AppsRates
Savings RatesLoan RatesVISA RatesFee ScheduleFinancial Education
Financial Education (Balance)Financial CounselingMortgage Help (Foreclosure)Fraud AlertsUnderstanding Your Credit Report and ScoresStudents
Student BankingGraduatesContact UsLocationHours and HolidaysAfter Hours Depository
